{
    "subject": "resource/Asya_(singer)",
    "predicate": "property/shortDescription",
    "object": "Turkish singer",
    "human_readable": "Asya is a Turkish singer.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6797046661376953,
            "question": "Is Asya a famous singer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6446340680122375,
            "question": "Is Asya a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47101151943206787,
            "question": "Does Asya sing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41838201880455017,
            "question": "Where has Asya performed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3753372132778168,
            "question": "What is Asya known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36092814803123474,
            "question": "What kind of music does Asya perform?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35360458493232727,
            "question": "Where is Asya from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30827057361602783,
            "question": "What nationality is Asya?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17273208498954773,
            "question": "What profession does Asya have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08580572158098221,
            "question": "Has Asya released any albums?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Asya is a Turkish singer.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1530_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What profession does Asya have?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1530_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality is Asya?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1530_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Asya from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1530_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1530_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1530_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1530_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1530_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1530_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1530_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1530_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1530_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1530_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1530_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Asya is a Turkish singer.\" The details about her being born in Eski\u015fehir, Turkey, and having a career as a pop singer are consistent with this claim."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}